University and Student Organizations and Societies - Record Group 39 WLU.RG.0039
Washington and Lee University, University Library Special Collections and Archives
- Faculty Organizations
  - Washington and Lee Chapter of the American Association of University College Professors (AAUP), 1935-1952
    This collection includes the constitution and minutes of monthly AAUP meetings at Washington and Lee.Typed and handwritten documents are includedpresent,and many of the pages are glued into an old ledger book,scrapbook style.
  - Washington and Lee Faculty Discussion Club, 1952-1965
    A collection of the minutes of the Faculty Discussion Club recorded during their irregular meetings during the late fifties into the mid-sixties.
  - Faculty, Washington and Lee University, brochure., 1970
- In Memoriam and A Celebration of the Life, 2002-2013
  - Morrison Curtis Bethea Jr. 1979-2002, 2002-04-04
  - Herman W. Taylor Jr., March 12, 1935-December 27-2002, 2003-01-10
  - Stephen Cullum Owings, Jr. 1980-2002, 2003-01-19
  - James Donagy, 2008-01-07
  - Remembering Robert E. Lee program postcard and luncheon buffet menu., 2013-10-14
- Archived Websites, 2015
  The University Library has captured the websites of some university and student organizations and societies using Archive-It. You can view these captures online.